-I...  -Yu, Yu, Yu!
不是我 鱼鱼鱼
The photos of you and Nan Bei were exposed!
你跟南北的图被曝光了
What photos of me and Nan Bei?
我跟南北有什么图
Look.
你看
Are they you and Nan Bei?
这是不是你跟南北
It's the hottest post on the BBS.
这是论坛上最火的帖子
It's updated every day.
每日都更新的
Danger!
有杀气
Hey, hey, hey!
哎哎哎
Okay. I admit it.
好好好 我承认
Sometimes,
我有的时候
I stole your
是偷偷拿你的
wet tissues to wipe my basketball.
湿巾擦篮球
No wonder my wet tissues usually twice a pack
我说两天一包
are used up so quickly!
这么快用完了呢
Wait.
不对
I don't come here
我找你来
for this!
不是因为这个事
Look!
你看
Are, are they...
这 这不是
Yes!
对呀
But we're not...
那我们又不是
I...
我
What do you mean?
什么意思啊
You also don't know this?
你也不知道这事
I... Of course not!
我 我当然不知道
I'm also one of the victims!
我也是受害者啊
Are they blind?
眼睛瞎了吗这帮人
How do we look like a couple?
我们哪儿像情侣了
Calm down.
先冷静啊
Let's analyze it.
我们分析一下
Who is likely to play such a dirty trick to us?
谁这么闲的倒腾我们
Photographer.
会摄影
Film editor.
会剪辑
Ah!
啊
I didn't do it! Really!
真不是我 真不是我
Look at those photos
你不信你看看
I took before!
我以前拍的那些作品
The composition
你这个构图
and post-production of yours are not professional!
后期就不是专业的
I, I'm professional!
我 我是专业的
What he said
他这么说
seems to make sense.
好像也有道理啊
Ouch.
哎哟
Hello, Manager.
喂 主管
Hao
小好
Xixi asked for a leave.
那个茜茜不是请假了吗
She has
她那儿
a contract of clients.
有一份客户的合同
It's not finished.
还没弄完
There are so many places to adjust.
要调的地方挺多的
You do it.
你来弄一下
Well...
这样
It will need at least one hour to adjust the contract.
改合同最快也要一小时
Maybe I'll skip the training.
要不训练一会儿不去了
No way.
不行 不行
It's an argument today. I cannot skip it.
今天是对辩 不能不去
Okay?
行吗
Yes.
嗯
Okay.
好
Jesus.
我天
Are you
你还在为
still mad at the post?
帖子的事生气呢
What's wrong with those people?
这都什么跟什么呀
Why are there so many
怎么还有这么多
likes and comments!
点赞跟评论
What the hell?
什么鬼
So sweet.
好甜呀
Go and get married.
滚去结婚
Opps! It's the feeling of heartbeat.
糟了 是心动的感觉
Nan Bei and me.
我跟南北
It's about Nan Bei and me.
这是我跟南北哎
How come do we look like a couple?
我们俩哪儿像情侣了
Do we look even close to
我们俩有一丁点
a couple?
配对的感觉吗
Tell me where we look like a couple.
你告诉我哪儿像了
Where?
哪儿好了
I'll correct myself.
我来改还不行
Actually...
其实吧
You...
你
Why did you also buy these pair of shoes?
你为什么也买这双鞋
Aren't they limited edition?
那不是限量的吗
It is the limited edition activity.
限量款活动吧
I thought only I got these.
我还以为就我抢到了呢
They've already been clichés.
现在都烂大街了
You tied your shoelaces differently.
你这鞋带系法不一样啊
Why?
怎么了
Let me tell you.
我跟你讲
If shoelaces are tied
鞋带要是
in a plain way,
系得不好看的话
like hairstyles of a person,
就跟人的发型一样
it will be so strange when it doesn't match the person.
不合适就特别奇怪
I have a new method to tie shoelaces.
有一个新的系法
Let me teach you.
我教你
It sounds great.
好听的
Honey. If you treat it in such a way,
大姐 你这么处理画面
every two can be a couple.
谁跟谁没情侣感
What are you eating?
你吃的什么
Blueberry biscuits.
蓝莓饼干
I made them by myself.
我自己做的
Do you want to have one?
你要不要尝一个
Okay.
好啊
Ma Nan. Pass me the eraser.
马楠 橡皮递我一下
Hmm.
嗯
What you said
你这么说
does make sense.
好像也有点道理
See?
看吧
But there's
可是这也是
still no way we can do about it.
无可奈何的事情啊
You should know
你要知道
that you two
你们两个
are undoubtedly
现在在大家眼里
a real couple
就是开了滤镜
for others.
和升格了呀
Rock Tea.
岩茶呢
As its name implies, where there's rock, there's tea.
顾名思义岩岩有茶
Where there's no rock, there's no tea.
非岩不茶
It tastes rich and mellow, and shows its quality in the water.
口感醇厚 水中有质感
Besides, favor remains after people drink it.
而且饮后余味绵长
Please.
请
Do you want to drink, Xiaoyu?
小鱼喝不喝
No.
不要
How's that?
怎么样
Brilliant!
好茶
You know,
我跟你说
you've really taken advantage of it.
你们真是占大便宜了
The tea is 500 yuan per kilo.
这个茶二百五十元一斤
Why don't you buy some
你们还不赶紧多买点儿
and taste it whenever you like?
回去慢慢品尝
Bro
大哥
Aren't we here for the training?
我们不是来训练的吗
You come here to sell things?
做起买卖来了
Drinking tea is to cultivate our mind
喝喝茶 陶冶情操
and get rid of distractions.
去除杂念嘛
There's still one who's not here.
人没齐呀
Where is Sister Tao Hao?
陶好姐呢
She said
陶好姐说
she would be here soon.
她一会儿就来了
Alright.
行吧
Wait for a while.
慢慢等吧
Sister Tao Hao
陶好姐
Hello.
你好呀
Sorry. Sorry.
不好意思 不好意思
Hao
小好姐
I'm late.
来晚了
Today's argument
咱们今天对辩
should be free debating or grouping?
是乱残 还是分组
Grouping, grouping.
分组 分组
Every time we choose free debating,
每次乱残到最后
I'm always the one who is beaten!
致残的都是我
Follow me.
跟着我
I'll help you.
哥 罩着你
Jesus Christ! I'll help you!
哎哟我的妈 哥罩着你
Okay.
那行吧
I'll be in a group with Hao.
那我跟小好姐一组
Come on.
来呀
She fell asleep so fast.
这么快就睡着了
She could fall asleep even if we were so noisy!
咱们这么吵都能睡着
How tired she is!
她得累成啥样
It's normal.
其实也正常
Vice president of seven clubs.
七个社团副社长
Vice minister of three student departments.
三个学生部副部长
It's already good that
没去陪老教练
she doesn't help the old coach.
就已经不错了
Let me have a look.
让我来看一下
One, apply for the budget for clubs.
一 申请社团经费
Two, reimburse for Mr. Li.
二 帮李主任报销
Three, the student union...
三 学生会
It's alright.
还好啊
There are only five to-do-lists.
也就五个待办事项
Although she's busier
虽然比我们
than five of us,
五个货忙了一点
I don't think she's terribly busy.
但是我觉得也不至于
Let me have a look.
我看一眼
Oh, oh, oh.
喔 喔 喔
I...
我
Fifty-six to-do-lists.
五十六个待办事项
Two of them are about you.
还有两个是你的
Help Nan Bei order the court.
帮南北订球场
Can't you order it yourself?
你自己不会订啊
Help Nan Bei order
帮南北订一家
an stylish restaurant.
有格调的饭店
Why can't you browse DianPing?
你自己不能大众点评吗
Why...why do you need
你 你要有格调的
an stylish restaurant?
饭店干什么
Don't your parents run a braised chicken restaurant?
黄焖鸡不是你家的吗
Wait a moment.
不是 你等会儿
There are also lists about you.
这不看还有你的吗
Xiaoyu's detergent powder.
小鱼的洗衣粉
Can't you buy it yourself?
洗衣粉你不会买啊
Help Xiaoyu return books.
替小鱼还书
Mu Xiaoyu
牧小鱼
I have to
我这就得
educate you now.
教育教育你
You've been more than 50 kilograms.
你一个一百多斤的人了
How can't you return books?
你说你还书你不会
Don't you have self-care ability?
你自理能力你没有
No, I... I mean,
不 我 我是说你那个
if you want to return books
你 你还书啊什么的
that are too heavy for you,
你要是嫌太重你还不了
I can help you.
我可以帮你还啊
Piss off.
走开
Ma Nan
马楠
Why does she help you to give out leaflets?
怎么还有帮你发传单
For what?
你发传单干嘛
I bought too much tea.
我这不是茶叶囤太多了
So I want to have a sale promotion.
要点促销活动吗
Jesus! You!
我的天哪 你们几个
Poor girl!
小好姐真可怜
She's so tired!
都这样了
Let us help her to handle some things.
咱们帮她解决几个吧
You...
你
I'm sorry.
不好意思
If you didn't wake up,
你要再不起来
I would become paralyzed.
我就半身不遂了
Hao
小好姐
Wait for a while.
等我一下
I'm almost done.
我马上就贴完了
Xiaoyu, let me do it.
小鱼 我来吧这
It's okay.
哎呀 没事
Hao
小好姐
The application lists of clubs
社团的报名名单
have been finished for you.
我已经帮你列好了
Thank you. It's so kind of you.
谢谢 太麻烦你们了
I've been sleeping for so long!
我睡了这么久啊
The... the training today...
那 那我们今天的训练
Don't worry, Hao.
放心吧 陶好姐
We have already
我们都已经
finished our training.
完成训练任务了
Take a good rest today.
你今天就好好回去休息
Give yourself a break.
给自己放个假
Right.
对
Look how tired you are.
你看你平时这么累
Take a rest from time to time.
偶尔让自己放松一下
Take a sun bath. Look at the sky.
晒晒太阳 看看天空
Look how beautiful the sky is.
你看多好看 是吧
I've only worked for one afternoon,
我这才弄了一个下午
but my back aches already.
就腰酸背痛的
Hao need deal with so many
你说小好姐每天要处理
things every day.
那么多事情
It's likely for her to get a cervical spondylopathy
那还不得有颈椎病
or a slipped disc.
什么腰间盘突出
You clearly know
小好姐的人设
what kind of person she is.
你又不是不知道
Multi-tasker.
八爪鱼呗
How could you say like that?
你有没有人性啊
Hao doesn't know how to refuse others.
小好姐是不会拒绝别人
Do you think she is not busy?
你以为她不累啊
She's not like you,
都跟你似的
who looks so mean.
那一天贱馊的
As a man, I...
我一大老爷们 我
Were it not
我要不因为
your bad temper,
你那脾气我能
how could I be so mean!
我这么憋屈吗我
Fight back against me!
你反抗呀
I dare not do, but I dare think.
我不敢我还不能想想
Come here. Come here.
过来 过来
Duck!
鸭子
Give it a name.
要不起个名吧
It seems inappropriate to
老鸭子鸭子地叫
call it duck.
也怪不合适的
Right.
也是
Call it...
叫
Xiwang
喜旺吧
Happiness and wealth.
喜庆又旺财
It also means hope.
谐音还是希望
So good.
多好
What an idiot!
怕不是个智障
Is he, duck?
是不是 鸭子
Xiwang
喜旺
I've added
调研结果
the investigation result.
我已经加进去了
I'll send it to Mr. Li right away.
一会儿我就发给李主任
Alright.
嗯嗯
Don't worry.
放心吧
Have fun with Nan Bei.
你跟南北好好玩吧
Hao
小好
As to the expenditure
今年各个社团
of each club,
的资金用度方面
you should specify
超出额度的
those who exceed the limit.
要详细说明啊
Okay. Okay.
好的 好的
I'll send it soon.
我一会儿就发过来
The document of traffic rules
上次往返两校区
of shuttle between campuses
交通规范的文件
should be scanned before the meeting.
记得在会议上扫描一下
Got it.
好好好
Hello.
喂
Hao, are you busy?
小好 现在忙吗
No.
不忙
The client needs a
客户那边要一份
preliminary project scheme
初期的项目策划书
in a haste.
要得着急
Write it for me.
你弄一下
Alright.
好好好
I'll send it right away.
我一会儿马上发
Wait.
对了
Remember to send an e-mail to the client.
记得给客户发个邮件
And send the document in the meeting
上次开会的文件
together.
一块发过去
Okay. Right away.
好 马上
Hello. Yes?
喂 怎么了
Hao
小好
Have you finished doing the slides?
演示文稿做好了吗
I've been busy since then. I forgot.
我一直在忙 给忘了
I'm sorry.
不好意思
The teacher is pressing for it.
老师催着要呢
We should hand it in today.
说的是今天要交
If you are busy,
你要是忙就算了吧
I'll do it myself.
我自己弄吧
Don't be angry.
你别生气啊
I guarantee that I'll finish it tonight.
我晚上一定给你赶出来
Well, alright.
那好吧
Thank you.
辛苦你了
I have other things to do now.
那我这边还有点事
I'll call you later.
我忙完打给你
Okay.
好
Hao
小好姐
Why are you lying on the ground?
你干嘛躺地上啊
You can take a nap on the bed.
你困了你上床睡会儿呗
I'm fine.
没事
I was just doing exercise.
我就是运动运动
Bad taste!
什么眼光
What a bad taste they have!
怎么看的呀这是
What are you looking at?
看什么呢
I...
我
You're insane!
你有病啊
Why do you always
你没事
stand behind others?
你老站人身后干嘛
Did you see the campus post?
你看没看那个校内帖
Fans are insane.
粉丝们疯了
Let's post to clarify our relationship.
要不咱俩发个澄清帖吧
Come on.
得了吧
In this kind of gossip,
在这种舆论里边
do you think you can
你觉得可以
depend on yourself to
凭借一己之力
change others' thought?
改变大家想法吗
Then what should we do?
那怎么办呀
Leave it alone?
不管啊
In my opinion,
我觉得呀
if it's a misunderstanding
既然最开始
at the beginning,
就是一个误会
just be more careful in the future.
以后就多注意呗
Our campus is not that big.
学校反正就这么大点
As time passes by,
时间长了
people will know
大家也就知道
what on earth happened.
到底是怎么回事了
That's what I want to hear.
算你说了句人话
Being a team member with you
跟你组组合这事吧
is the least thing
反正我这辈子
I'll do again in my life.
不想经历第二次
Look at it by yourself.
你自己看看 你自己看
Do I owe you?
我亏你了 屈你了
Like a ghost. Check it out.
跟鬼一样 你看看
Look at it. Look. Look at it!
你看 你 你看 你自己看
Number eight. What's the big deal?
不就第八吗
Who cares?
谁会在乎一样
Take it easy.
别紧张
I'll go after fetching documents.
我拿个资料就走
What do you mean?
你什么意思
We are all victims
我们都是这篇
of "the best couple" post.
最佳组合帖的受害人
Liu Yanze and I
我跟刘彦泽
are also
也是他们
one of the couples they formed.
盲目配对的组合之一
However, compared to you,
不过跟你们相比呢
our condition is worse.
我们的情况更糟糕一些
The rank of Liu Yanze and I
我和刘彦泽的排名
is always the first.
一直都是第一
So annoying.
还挺烦的
Is that an annoyed appearance?
你那是烦的表情吗
You must enjoy it!
你很享受吧
Are you
你该不会是
mad because
因为我们排名
our ranking
比你们高
is higher than yours?
而生气了吧
Isn't it normal?
这不很正常吗
It's true.
还真是啊
The billboard
这个排行榜
is updated every week
每周都会更新一次
for revote.
重新投票
They always rank the first every week.
他们俩每周都是第一啊
Are...
你
you okay?
还好吧
These are the latest
这是最新一期的
photos and videos of couples.
情侣照片跟视频
Wait.
哎
If you continue to do it,
你这么下去
sooner or later,
早晚有一天
you will be exposed.
你会暴露身份的
Mu Xiaoyu won't let you go.
牧小鱼不会放过你的
You'll never know
我们磕糖少女的心
how we CP fans feel.
你是不会懂的
Then,
那就
wish you good luck.
祝你好运
Thanks for watching the weather forecast.
欢迎收看天气预报
Smog continues to gather in our city,
我市浓雾持续聚集
having a negative effect on
给市民的生产生活
the production and daily life of citizens.
带来非常不利的影响
Super smog gathering above our city
聚集在我市上升的
is predicted to
超强浓雾预计在
disperse tonight.
今夜得到驱散
The sunny day expected
那么大家期待已久的
for so long is coming.
艳阳天也即将到来
Excuse me.
不好意思啊
Sorry. I know I'm wrong.
对不起 我知道我错了
Don't be mad at me!
你不要生气嘛
If I watch a movie at my dormitory,
我在寝室看个电影
I can talk about the plot with my roommates.
还能跟室友聊个剧情
But you just look at your phone.
你就只会看手机
We only come out once a week.
咱们一礼拜只出来一次
There are only three hours to
吃饭加看电影
have dinner and watch a movie.
总共三个小时
Don't tell me
你告诉我
you cannot even give me
你现在连三个小时
three hours?
都给不了我了吗
But my junior and her boyfriend
可是学妹跟她男朋友
have been quarreling for so long.
都吵架这么久了
She cries so sadly.
她都哭成这样了
I cannot leave her alone.
我总不能不管她吧
What makes a difference
晚两个小时劝她
if you comfort her two hours later?
有什么区别呢
You always care about others'
你总那么关心别人
relationship.
的感情生活
How about ours?
我们的呢
Sorry.
对不起
I may
我可能
be under great pressure during internship.
最近实习压力太大了
Don't have dinner this evening.
晚饭就别一起吃了
Why don't you have
你这儿为什么没有
Yao Shen instant noodles?
姚申牌泡面
I'm sorry.
不好意思啊
The last one
最后一碗泡面
is bought by that lady.
被那位女士买走了
Senior
学长
What a coincidence!
这么巧
You, you can eat mine.
要 要不你吃我这碗吧
I haven't eaten it.
我还没有吃过呢
Is it proper to eat yours?
这样不太好吧
It's okay.
没事
Alright.
那好吧
It would be better if there are pickles.
要是有咸菜就好了
I know a kind of pickles
我知道有个牌子
which tastes so good.
特别好吃
Senior
学长
It would be better if there are sausages.
要是有香肠就更好了
I'll buy it.
我去拿
Try it, Senior.
试试 学长
Any drink?
有喝的吗
Coke?
可乐
Senior
学长
Hello, Manager.
喂 主管
Hao
小好
Didn't I tell you
不是说
to send the email to the client before leaving work?
下班前发给客户的吗
The client said he didn't receive it at the end of the day!
客户说下班前都没收到
Sorry, Manager.
对不起 主管
I was two minutes late.
我晚了两分钟
But I've
但是我已经
apologized in the e-mail.
在邮件里道过歉了
What's the point of apology?
道歉有什么用啊
Xixi asked for a leave these days.
茜茜这几天请假
There's only you who
部门做事的
can do these things.
就剩下你一个人
Why did you do things
你怎么做事
without consideration?
还缺根筋呐你
Manager, I...
主管我
What?
你什么你
Remember:
记着啊
Be serious
以后做事
at work!
长点脑子
Sorry.
对不起
Give me some tissues.
你给我拿包纸
Here you are.
给
I'll pay you later.
等会儿给你啊
One day, when I walked home,
我有一天散步回家
I came across a magic lamp.
碰到一个神灯
I wiped it with a cloth,
我就拿布擦了擦
and an elf popped out of it.
蹦出来一个精灵
He told me that
他跟我说
he could grant me a wish.
他可以满足我一个愿望
Whatever I wanted.
要什么都可以
However,
但是
once your wish came true,
一旦满足了你这个愿望
your enemy,
你的仇人
whom you hated most,
你这辈子最恨的那个人
would get
会得到你
the same twice as much.
所得到的东西的一倍
Therefore,
于是乎
I made a wish:
我就许了一个愿
Every day in my life,
在我接下来的每一天
every day,
每一天
I can sleep for twelve hours.
都能睡够十二个小时
How's that?
怎么样
Is it great?
棒不棒
I've heard it before.
我听过了
Oh.
啊
I don't notice that you
我也没看你
have an internship outside.
在外面实习呀
My boyfriend's manager
是我男朋友的主管
is too busy.
他太忙了
I help him
我就替他
to do part of the work.
分担一部分工作
So you have work at university,
所以你在学校有工作
in the debate team,
在辩论队也有工作
and you also
然后出来
help your boyfriend to work.
还得帮男朋友干工作
Why?
为什么呀
When I was in Junior 3,
初三那年
my sister was born.
我妹妹出生了
I had to
我只能
make myself more thoughtful
让自己变得更懂事
and more obedient
更听话
to gain my parents' attention.
来获得爸爸妈妈的关注
Hao, eat with us.
小好来吃饭了
Dad, Mom. You eat first.
爸妈 你们先吃吧
After she falls asleep,
我把她哄睡了
I'll come to eat.
我就过来吃
Because of my parents' jobs,
因为父母工作的关系
we often moved house.
我们家也经常搬家
Every time we moved,
每次搬家
I should get into
我都要进入
a new school to study.
新的学校环境学习
As a transfer student,
而作为一个转校生
I felt it hard to
我很难融入
integrate into the class.
班级原有的集体之中
I had no friends in the class.
我在班里没有朋友
Later...
后来
Class is over.
今天课就上到这里
Let's call it a day.
放学
I'll go now.
我先走了
Bye-bye.
拜拜
Let's go home together.
我们放学一起回家呀
But I'm on duty today.
可是我要值日
You can go first.
要不你先走吧
I can help you.
我帮你一起啊
You're so nice!
你人真好
Let's do it.
走吧
Okay.
嗯
So from then on,
所以自打那以后
you started to gain attentions
你就开始通过讨好别人
by pleasing others.
来获得关注
Tao Hao
陶好
This is not right.
你这是病
What should I do?
那怎么办呀
Correct it!
治啊
So, Tao Hao.
所以 陶好
Your situation is very severe now.
你现在已经病入膏肓了
In order not to affect
为了不影响
the routine of our team,
队里的日常生活
let's start to
咱们现在就开始
train you now.
训练吧
Okay.
行
Just tell me,
那你们说吧
how to correct me?
怎么治
From now on, refuse every request
从现在开始拒绝掉一切
that you want to refuse.
你想拒绝的要求
Oh.
啊
Well...
这
Is it easy?
叫简单啊
Of course.
当然了
Let's have a try.
咱们先试一下吧
Who'll go first?
谁先来
I'll do!
我来
Okay. You go first.
好 那你来
Hao
小好姐啊
We'll clean our dormitory tomorrow.
明日寝室打扫卫生
You do it by yourself.
你一个人去吧
Okay.
好
What?
啊
Dear me!
哎呀
It doesn't work!
你提的这个
Our dormitory
那宿舍卫生不是
is always cleaned up
每次都是小好姐
by Hao.
打扫的吗
Your turn.
你来
Hao
小好姐
I don't want to write for the first debater.
一辩的稿子我不想写了
please help me.
你替我写吧
When I searched for materials yesterday,
昨天我查资料的时候
I've finished it.
已经写完了
What?
啊
Hao
小好姐
I was just joking!
我给你开玩笑的呀
You should refuse us!
你得拒绝我们呀
Well,
不是
because our friendship
大家主要是
is so good!
都关系太好了
If it's from someone else, I may succeed.
换别人没准我能成功的
Your solution doesn't work!
你这也不行啊
It's okay.
没事
I have faith in her.
我对她有信心
I believe her.
我相信她的
Do you have any
下个星期的
problems of jobs next week?
工作有什么问题吗
No problem.
没问题
You didn't write anything.
你一个字都没写
Of course you have no problems!
肯定没问题啊
I have a good memory.
我脑子好使
Really?
你脑子好使
Why haven't you graduated?
怎么还没毕业呢
Sorry.
不好意思
I'm late.
我来晚了
Hao. Take your time.
小好 不着急啊
Take your time.
不着急
Well, Hao.
那个 小好
Did you finish the table
社团费用的表格
of club fees?
做好了吗
Yes.
好了
Here it is.
在这儿
Have a look.
来 看一下
Have a look. Mr. Li.
李主任 你看一下
These are the clarification of
这个是三个社团
cost overruns of three clubs,
的超支费用说明
and schedule
还有模拟规范
for the experimental shuttle
校园班车的
between campuses.
时间章程
Please sign over there.
需要您签个字
Okay. There are only two of them.
行 这只有两家啊
Oh.
噢
This is the third one.
还有一家在这儿呢
Hao. It's of the last year.
小好 这是去年的
See? It has been signed.
你看都签过字了
Sorry.
不好意思
I'll print it right now.
我马上再去打一份
No, no, no. Thanks.
不用了 不用了 不用了
No need.
不用了
Oh, right.
对了
Who'd like to send the document
管院的那个文件
to the School of Management?
你们谁去送一下
I'll do it. Mr. Li.
我去吧 李主任
You need to take a rest.
你得注意休息了啊
You send it for me after a while.
一会儿你去一下吧
Okay?
好吧
Thank you, Mr. Li.
谢谢李主任
Okay. I won't bother you now.
行 那你们先忙
I'll go for a meeting.
我去开个会
Nailed it.
好了
Goodbye, Mr. Li.
李主任再见
Hello.
喂
Watch a movie?
看电影啊
But I'm busy in the student union this afternoon.
可是我下午学生会有事
How about this evening?
不然晚上吧
The last movie is in this afternoon.
下午最后一场了
Alright.
好吧
Hao
小好姐
Could you please
你下午能不能
help me to send the document
帮我去管院
to the School of Management?
送一份文件啊
Okay.
嗯
Thank you, Hao!
谢谢小好姐
Hey.
哎
I'll go with you.
我陪你去
And I'll bring you to a place.
顺便带你去一个地方
Okay.
嗯
No matter
今天不管他
how hard he plays,
弹得有多认真
or how good he plays,
弹得有多好
don't give him a penny.
你一分钱不能给他
You'll win if you listen to five songs.
坚持五首歌 你就赢了
This song is for my dad
这首歌送给我
who's ill abed.
卧病在床的父亲
Hold it.
忍住
The next song is for my sister
下一首歌送给我
who is born
天生
to have a harelip.
兔嘴的妹妹
Hum?
嗯
What's that?
这是什么
I, I really don't know it.
我 我真的不知道
I didn't know why it just came out...
我也不知道它怎么就
Take it back.
收回去吧
Fine. Give it to him.
给给给给
I...
我
Do you have QR code?
可以二维码扫码吗
Yes.
可以呀
♪ I've been racing with youth ♪
我与青春一路在赛跑
♪ Every second is good ♪
每一秒都美好
♪ This one-direction track ♪
这一路单向的轨道
♪ is full of gunpowder ♪
满满地蓄着火药
Right now,
现在这个时间
the debating room belongs to them.
辩论室是他们的
Who knows if
谁知道这个时间
they'll come?
他们会不会来
Not here.
没来
Wow! How dare they changed the lock!
嚯 竟然换锁
Despicable! Dirty! Rascally!
卑鄙 下流 死无赖
Did you unlock it
你是不是打开
in a wrong way?
方式不对呀
Let me try.
我试试
They did change it!
真换锁了
Filthy! Disgusting! Bastard!
龌龊 恶心 下三烂
Right!
是吧
Whatever.
不管了
It's not an electric lock.
这也不是电子锁
Get out of the way.
走开
Hurry up.
快点啊
I...
我
Do I need to ask the guard
要我把保安
to look at this?
叫过来围观吗
Yin Nan, Yin Nan.
殷楠呐 殷楠
You are what you're called!
你可真不愧叫殷楠呐
You're sinister and cunning!
你真是又阴又难哪
Tell me why you changed the lock.
你告诉我凭什么换锁
We also need to use the classroom!
教室我们也要用啊
Haven't you learned
学校防火防盗的
the knowledge of
安全知识
fire alarm and security in our university?
还没普及到你那儿吗
We're also a debate team.
我们也是辩论队
Don't go too far.
你不要太过分
Forget it. Forget it.
算了 算了 算了
Not worth it. Not worth it.
不值得 不值得
As for the final interpretation right,
关于最终解释权的问题
I've made it clear.
我已经说过了
If you don't understand it,
还有什么不明白的
ask the one beside you
多问问你身边这个
who learns the law as a dabbler.
学法律的半吊子吧
Who's the dabbler!
谁是半吊子呀
Not worth it. Not worth it.
不值得 不值得 不值得
Can I be happy by watching it?
看这个我能开心吗
Could you throw
你下次能不能
your own phone next time?
摔自己的手机呀
Sa has been teaching us:
小撒不是一直教咱们吗
Don't be angry.
莫生气
Life is like a game.
人生就像一场戏
I've heard you just picked a lock.
听说你刚刚撬锁了
I finally know that
原来你学法律
you study the law
就是为了在
to be on the edge of breaking the law.
法律的边缘疯狂试探
Does it work?
好使吗
Maybe.
凑合吧
Hello, Dango.
喂 团子
Hello, Xiaoyu.
喂 小鱼
I have a meeting in the comic club.
我这边漫画社有个会
I cannot make it there.
过不去了
Don't forget Hao's
别忘了小好姐
birthday cake.
的生日蛋糕
It depends on you and Nan Bei.
靠你和南北了
I see. I see. I see.
知道了 知道了 知道了
Go ahead.
你去吧
Alright.
好了
Hurry up. Nan Bei.
赶紧吃吧 南北
We should prepare...
咱们得准备
Where's the dessert I left here?
我刚才留下的甜点呢
I'll throw it up for you.
我给你吐出来
Here you are.
给
Thank you.
谢谢啊
Thank you for your company.
谢谢你陪我
It's on me.
我请客
Okay.
好
Hello.
你好
I need two strawberry ice creams.
我要两个草莓冰淇淋
Okay. Eighteen yuan in total.
好的 一共十八
Isn't it 12 yuan for each?
不是十二块一个吗
Did you make it wrong?
是不是算错了
Our store has a discount today.
今天我们店做活动
Half price for the second for couples.
情侣第二份半价
Well, we're not a couple.
那个 我们不是情侣
Not yet?
还不是啊
Have you bought them?
好了吗
Right away.
马上就好
I'll look for seats.
那我先找位置去
Okay.
嗯
Consider the couple discount.
情侣套餐考虑一下
Senior
学长
Did you watch a movie
你有没有看
released lately
最近新出了一个电影
called "There is a Wood in the North"?
叫北方有木头
Nope.
没有
Several days ago, my boyfriend
前两天我男朋友
brought me to watch it.
带我去看了
It's good.
挺好看的
Oh.
噢
The downstairs of the cinema
电影院楼下
is a Hong Kong style cafe.
还有一家港式茶餐厅
After watching the movie,
我们看完电影之后
my boyfriend had dinner with me there.
我男朋友也带我去吃了
Oh.
哦
What's the matter?
你怎么了
I'm fine.
我没事
I, Senior, I...
我 学长 我
My boyfriend is called Shi Jinxian.
我男朋友叫石近贤
What do I care?
关我什么事啊
Oh.
哦
Just chatting.
没事就闲聊嘛
Hello. Do you have an order?
你好 请问有预约吗
Yes.
有
Dumb Mu.
木鱼脑袋
Wait a moment.
稍等
Miss Mu, right?
牧小姐是吗
Please sign over here.
麻烦这边签个字
Okay.
好
Thank you.
谢谢
You're welcome.
不客气
Are you going to make it alone
请问是你们一个人做
or by both of you?
还是两个人一起
Make, make what?
做 做什么
DIY cake means
自己动手蛋糕
making the cake yourself.
当然是要自己动手做呀
Wait me for a while.
稍等我一下
If you cannot
你要是
explain it to me why we should
一句话给我解释不清楚
make the cake by both of us
为什么要两个人
with one sentence,
一起做蛋糕的话
the thing that will be baked
一会儿放在烤箱里
will be your head.
就是你的脑袋
Slow down. Slow down.
慢点 慢点 慢点
Smoke ahead.
前面有人封烟
There must be four of them.
应该是个满编队
Got it. Got it.
好好好
Come on.
来来来
Get on the car. Circle shrank.
上车 上车 缩圈了
Wait! I haven't got on the car!
哎呀 别 我还没上去呢
-Hurry up!  -Wait for me!
快快快 等等我 等等我
Wait for me. Wait for me.
等我一下 等我一下 等
Hurry up, bro!
快点儿 大哥
Come on. Get on the car.
来来来 上车 上车
Wait me for a while.
等一下 等一下啊
Hurry up.
你快点啊
No way. I can't handle it.
不行 我撑不住了
Right away. Right away!
你快快快
I come back.
回来了 回来了
Wait a minute.
你别急啊
Let, let me ask you:
就我 我先问你
How does Hao treat us?
小好姐对咱们怎么样
Good.
好
Hao
小好姐
treats us so well.
既然对咱们这么好
Today is her birthday.
今天又是她生日
So we shouldn't
咱们是不是就
find a cake that is
不能在货架上
so common
随随便便找
on the rack to her,
一个普普通通的蛋糕
right?
送给她
Yes.
不能
So,
所以啊
how can we find a way that is
咱们怎么找到一个
original,
又有新意
ingenious,
别出心裁的
and meaningful?
还有意义的
We must
咱们必须得
make a cake by ourselves.
自己亲手做一个蛋糕
Am I right?
对不对
Do you know how to make it?
你会做吗
Do I
我会做
do things without preparation?
自己没有准备的事情吗
This rough style...
这种粗犷的风格
Excuse me.
麻烦
Let a baker teach us.
来个糕点师教一下
The red light lasts for such a long time.
这个红灯还挺久的
The setting time of traffic lights
红绿灯的设置时间
depends on vehicle volume.
取决于汽车通行量
It's a four-lane double way.
这是双向四车道
There are universities around it.
附近都是大学城
So, it should be over two minutes.
所以在两分钟以上吧
There are still two minutes left?
还有两分钟啊
Right.
对呀
Only less than one minute is passed.
这才一分钟不到
As long as two people
只要两个人
have a tacit mutual understanding,
有足够的默契
they can shut up
就能闭嘴
and enjoy a moment of silence.
享受片刻的沉默
Aren't you embarrassed?
所以你不尴尬吗
Of course I am.
尴尬得要死
But embarrassment is normal.
但是尴尬就是人生常态
You need to get used to it.
习惯就好
By the way,
再说了
it's you who are more embarrassed.
是你比较尴尬吧
Tao Hao
陶好
Senior
学长
You're good-looking.
你挺好看的
But I have no interest in you.
但是我对你没兴趣
Why?
为什么
No.
不对
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm the one who likes freedom.
我是一个崇尚自由的人
Relationship for me
我觉得谈恋爱这种事
is too troublesome.
对我来说太麻烦了
If I have to find one, I'll find a wife.
要谈就找一个能结婚的
If you were
但是如果你
the one as my wife,
作为我的结婚对象的话
I couldn't imagine
我就真的无法想象
how boring it would be
婚后生活会有
of my life after marriage.
多疲倦 多
S...Senior
学 学长
You've already elaborated your opinion.
您已经阐述您的观点了
I know what you mean.
我知道您的意思了
I noticed that
我是看你从
you were a little bit nervous
冰淇淋店里面出来
from the ice cream store.
就有点紧张
I just want to clarify it.
我就想澄清一下
I think
我就是觉得
you and I are alone,
咱俩孤男寡女的
so it's not appropriate
走在街上
to be noticed on the street.
被人看到不太好
There are so many people.
这茫茫人海的
Who cares about you?
谁看你了
Senior, you don't know it.
学长 你是不知道
My boyfriend
我男朋友啊
often brought me
他经常带我来
to go shopping on the street.
这条街逛街
We also often ate
这家火锅店
in the hotpot restaurant.
我们也经常来吃
Every time, we would
我们每次都
sit at that place...
坐在那个位置